In this application, a graph models a social network among characters in Marvel comic books. Each node in the graph represents a character, and an edge ⟨Char1,Char2⟩ indicates that Char1 appeared in a comic book that Char2 also appeared in. There will be a separate edge for every comic book, labeled with the name of the book. For example, if Zeus and Hercules appeared in five different issues of a given series, then Zeus would have five edges to Hercules, and Hercules would have five edges to Zeus. The graph does not store reflexive edges from characters to themselves. 

The class MarvelPaths reads the Marvel data from a file (marvel.csv), builds a graph, and finds paths between characters in the graph. 